wmsn mission statement draft

Mission Statement: 
We have a Strong campaign to spread our message to all the importance of Awareness, Safety and Self Protection . We want to share our knowledge and training with others so they can be empowered to experience life in a positive and fulfilling way.live a well rounded life. We want to teach in our local communities but want to share our message world wide . 

By signing up on our site , you will get to hear our Voices , and share the same dreams of making this world a better and safer place for all . 

Women make some noise 
Take that first step and sign up 
Name: 
Email: 
Phone #: 

Master Gina PinPin,
 
Thank you for the training you provide my team. The women of NSI started the self-defense to gain some safety tools and awareness. This is particularly important because we have an early start in the morning - 5:30. We felt concerned for their safety in the parking lot – walking in the dark from their car to the office. However, the training has become is much more than gaining some safety tools and awareness! It has help build more teamwork, team unity and camaraderie. The staff has expressed how much confidence the training has provided them. In a worst case situation, they feel more armed to defend themselves; but more importantly, they have expressed how much more they are aware of their surroundings.  They love learning new techniques of how to protect themselves. They also love the intense physical workout. They feel like they are growing stronger and this has helped them with their self-confidence and body image. The cardio workouts are great and they like getting to work out and learn together!  
 
Kind regards, 
Jill B. Jay, Ph.D. 
jjaynsi@msn.com 

​